Guide to the Cornell Alumni Association records,1932-2013.
Cornell Alumni Association records
- Series III. Committees
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Alumnae Secretary Committee (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Publicity Committee (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Auditing Committee (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - New York Dinner for Mr. Malott, February 7, 1951, February 7, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Robert J. Kane Dinner, January 17, 1956, January 17, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Promotion for Syracuse Dinner, January-April 1958, January-April 1958 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Chicago Regional Meeting, January 31, 1959, January 31, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Cincinnati Regional Meeting, February 7, 1959, February 7, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Chicago Regional Meeting, February 1, 1958, February 1, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Boston Regional Meeting, March 29, 1958, March 29, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Chicago Regional Meeting, 1959, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Pittsburgh Regional Conference, April 30, 1960, April 30, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Reports of the Federation Scholarship Fund, 1938-1941, 1938-1941 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Papers Describing the Federation Scholarship Fund, 1936-1940, 1936-1940 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Letters Requesting Feedback from Cornell Federation Scholars, 1961-1964, 1961-1964 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Special Committee Notes (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Secondary Schools Committee (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Scholarship Finance Committee (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Nominating Committee (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Election Committee (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Credentials Committee (Women's Clubs) (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Placement Committee (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Executive Committee (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Committee on Alumni Trustee Nominations, 1970-1979 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Trustee Committee Report, 1938 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Federation Scholarship Committee, 1941-1947 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Federation Scholarship Drive - Ithaca, 1940 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Alumni Leadership Development and Training Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Alumni News Committee, 1990-1992 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Awards Committee, 1979-1988 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Careers and Summer Jobs Committee, 1991-1997 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Club Affairs Committee, 1991-1996 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Community Service, 1991-1993 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Community Service, 1993-1997 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Elections Committee, 1991-1993 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Federation of Cornell Clubs, 1979-1992 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Liaison Committee, 1986-1990 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Minority Affairs, 1991-1993 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Nominating Committee, 1976-1992 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Nominating Committee, 1992-1994 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Nominating Committee, 1994-1997 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Nominating Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Nominating Committee, 1998-2000 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Nominating Committee, 2001-2002 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Nominating Committee, 2002-2004 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Nominating Committee, 2004-2006 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Nominating Committee, 2007-2008 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Programs Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Recognition Committee, 1981-1991 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Recognition Committee, 1991-1998 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Regional Workshop Task Force, 1991-1992 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Scholarship Challenge Grant, 1987-1989 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1988-1993 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1994-2000 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Scholarship Committee, 2001-2007 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Stars Scholarship Program, 1990-1993 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Technology Committee, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Training Committee, 2000-2001 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Ways and Means Committee, 1992-2002 (Box 19, Folder 28)
- Series IV. Scholarships, Awards, and the Federation Scholarship Awards Committee
  - Senior Award: Federation of Cornell Men's Clubs, 1948-1954 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Misc. Scholarship (Financial Aid) Applications (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Scholarship Application- Stamey, M.J. (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Scholarship Application- Houghton, N.E. (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Misc. Scholarship (Financial Aid) Applications (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Scholarship Application- Mattinew, E.M. (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Scholarship Application- Scott, J.C. (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Scholarship Application- Links, C.H. (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Scholarship Application- Bates, L. (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Scholarship Application- Perry, D.M. (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Scholarship Application- Tuthill, S. (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Scholarship Application- Taylor, R.L. (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Scholarship Application- Finegold, D.R. (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Scholarship Offers (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Blank Scholarship Application Forms (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Federation Scholarship Committee Memberships (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Federation Scholarship Committee- Meeting Minutes (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Federation Scholarship Committee- Correspondence to Cornell Women's Clubs (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Federation Scholarship Committee- Members' Correspondence (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Federation Scholarship Committee- Directors' Correspondence (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Federation Scholarship Committee- General Correspondence (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Federation Scholarship Holders (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Federation Scholarship Committee- Final Report (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Incomplete Scholarship Applications (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Federation Scholarship Committee- Considered Applicants (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Federation Scholarship Committee- Rejected Applicants, 1957-1958 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Federation Scholarship Committee- Meeting Information and Offer Letters, 1955-1957 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Nellie M. Lewis Scholarship Applications, 1954-1955 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Federation Scholarship Award Value Statements (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Scholarship Finance Committee (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Dearstyne Scholarship Fund (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Frances Johnson Crofts Scholarship Fund (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Ida H. Hyde Scholarship Fund (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Margaret Crouch Nottingham Scholarship Fund (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Clara G. Cornell Scholarship Fund (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Ruth Darville Memorial Scholarship (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Sarah G. Blanding Gift, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Federation Scholarship Committee- Applications (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Federation Scholarship Committee- Applications (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Federation Scholarship Committee- Applications (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Federation Scholarship Committee- Applications (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Federation Scholarship Committee- Applications (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Federation Scholarship Endowment Fund, Late 1940s-1950s, Late 1940s-1950s (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Federation Scholarship Endowment Fund, September 1959-July 1961, September 1959-July 1961 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Contribution from the Cornell Women's Clubs to the Federation Scholarship Endowment Fund, 1960-1962, 1960-1962 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Federation Scholarship Endowment Fund, July 1961-June 1962, July 1961-June 1962 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Federal Scholarship Endowment Fund, 1946-1951, 1946-1951 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Federal Scholarship Endowment Fund, 1951-1958, 1951-1958 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Federal Scholarship Endowment Fund, 1956-1960, 1956-1960 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Scholarship Applications, Fall 1941, Fall 1941 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Scholarship Applications, January 1942-February 1943, January 1942-February 1943 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Scholarship Applications, February 1943-March 1946, February 1943-March 1946 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Federal Scholarship Awards Committee Correspondence, February 1958-May 1959, February 1958-May 1959 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Federal Scholarship Endowment Fund (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Scholarship Organizational Papers (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Scholarship Fund, 1934-36 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Scholarship Fund, 1937 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Scholarship Fund, Jan - May 1938 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Scholarship Fund, June - Dec 1938 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Scholarship Fund, 1939 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Scholarship Fund, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Federation of Cornell Women's Clubs- Scholarship Fund (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Federation of Cornell (Women's) Clubs- Scholarship Listings (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - French Scholarship Fund, 1917-1922 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Federation Scholarship Fund, 1938-1940 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - National Scholarships, 1946-1948 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Outstanding Senior Award, 1973-1984 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Frank Rhodes Exemplary Alumni Service Award, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Frank Rhodes Exemplary Alumni Service Award, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Frank Rhodes Exemplary Alumni Service Award, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Frank Rhodes Exemplary Alumni Service Award, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Frank Rhodes Exemplary Alumni Service Award, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Frank Rhodes Exemplary Alumni Service Award, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Frank Rhodes Exemplary Alumni Service Award, 2002 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Frank H.T. Rhodes Exemplary Alumni Service Awards Dinner (length: 1:12:00), September 27, 2002 (Folder V-648)
  - Frank Rhodes Exemplary Alumni Service Award, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Frank Rhodes Exemplary Alumni Service Award Photographs, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Frank Rhodes Exemplary Alumni Service Award Photographs, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Frank Rhodes Exemplary Alumni Service Award, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Frank H.T. Rhodes Exemplary Alumni Service Awards Dinner (length: 1:07:15), October 15, 2004 (Folder V-702)
  - Frank Rhodes Exemplary Alumni Service Award, 2005 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Frank Rhodes Exemplary Alumni Service Award, 2006 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Frank Rhodes Exemplary Alumni Service Award, 2007 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Frank Rhodes Exemplary Alumni Service Award, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Frank Rhodes Exemplary Alumni Service Award, 2009 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Frank Rhodes Exemplary Alumni Service Award, 2010 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Frank Rhodes Exemplary Alumni Service Award, 2011 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Frank Rhodes Exemplary Alumni Service Award-includes DVD-#839, 2012 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Frank Rhodes Exemplary Alumni Service Award, 2013 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Series V. Additional Uncategorized Alumni Association Records and Information
  - Undergraduate- Alumni Relations (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Mortar Board Alumni Contact Information (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Maps of the USA (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Medical College Administrative Applicant Information (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Cornell Alumnae House Association (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - American Association of University Women (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Virginia Dunbar- Dean, Cornell School of Nursing (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Prospective Students (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Panhellenic (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Women's Self-Government Association (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Promotion of Women's Scientific Research (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - American Alumni Council, District II Conference, January 24-26, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Emblem of Cornell University (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Group Housing Plan (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - College Admissions Information (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Cornell Days/Mary Donlon Material (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence Concerning and with Mary Donlon, April 1935-March 1964, April 1935-March 1964 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence on the Construction of Mary Donlon Hall, 1960-November 1961, 1960-November 1961 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence on the Construction of Mary Donlon Hall, December 1961-February 1963, December 1961-February 1963 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper Articles on Mary Donlon Hall, Early 1960s, Early 1960s (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Contributions to Mary Donlon Hall, Early 1960s, Early 1960s, Early 1960s (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Marquette University Commencement, June 1961 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Bull's Eye Art Paper (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Booklets on Cornell (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Cornell Pamphlets (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Class Affairs Papers, 1950-1954, 1950-1954 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Class Affairs Papers, 1963-1964, 1963-1964 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Cornell Reunion Papers, 1956-1963, 1956-1963 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Cornell Reunion, Tentative Documents, 1963-1964, 1963-1964 (Box 8, Folder 9a)
  - Cornell Reunion Papers, 1960-1964, 1960-1964 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Cornell Reunion Papers, 1963, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Marion Quell Papers, C.U. Council, 1954-1964, 1954-1964 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Virginia Barthel Seipt '32 Papers, 1960-1964, 1960-1964 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - American Association of University Women, 1936-1939 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Coordination of General Alumni Activities (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Alumni Corporation and Foster Coffin Correspondence (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Alumni News, 1936-1939 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Cornell Day, 1934-1939 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Cornell Day at Home, 1936-1938 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Mary Donlon Campaign Material (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Mary Donlon Campaign Material, 1936 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Mary Donlon Campaign Material, January 1937 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Mary Donlon Campaign Material, February 1937 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Mary Donlon Campaign Material, March 1937 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Mary Donlon Campaign Material, Apr - Aug 1937 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Mary Donlon Campaign Material, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Mary Donlon Campaign Material (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Southern California Alumni Association (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Southern California Alumni Association, 1955-1958 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Southern California Alumni Association, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Southern California Alumni Association, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Southern California Alumni Association, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Alumni Association Board of Directors, 1958-1989 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Alumni Federation Historical Timeline, 1990-2008 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - By-Laws, 1973-2006 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Alumni Association Blanket, MU-1364 (Box 10)
  - CAAAN Tutorial, CD-1672
    Created by 'C'AC and funded by a grant from the Cornell Alumni Federation